

GRAPHICS • DESIGN • VIDEO • PHOTOGRAPHY

Graphic Design - Experience in print and multi media design. Effectively executed re-branding and design for specific use of clients industry. Experience with designing websites, logos, advertisements, and any other forms that is needed.

Video/ Photo - Experience in setting up multimedia equipment for live streaming and recording. Use of multiple software to create stunning and educational videos for clients. Able to understand clients wants in video production.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe IllustratorAdobe InDesignElementorAdobe PhotoshopFinal Cut Pro XGoogle DocsAdobe PremiereAdobe LightRoomAdobe AfterEffects

EXPERIENCE

DNG PRINTING & BRANDING SOLUTIONS

San Diego, CA.

www.dngprinting.com

Worked closely with clients to re-brand and execute their new look. Created, designed logos, websites and collateral material for clients needs.

BEREA INTERNATIONAL/ BEREA FILMS

Los Angeles, CA. / Guadalajara, Jalisco. Sep. 2015 - Aug. 2018

www.bereafilms.com

Filmed, edit and colored video for multimedia platforms. Worked with a team to film a documentary and get ready for distribution. Worked with multiple people to come up with design ideas for digital music platforms release.

MULTICOMM

San Dlego, CA. Oct. 2014 - Aug. 2015

www.multi-comm.com

Ran and installed cable lines for internet use. Handled all client situations on location and always made sure they were happy with their service.

LEGEND 3D

San Dlego, CA. Oct. 2008 - Aug. 2011

www.legend3d.com

Worked with proprietary software to turned 2D movies for viewing in 3D. Movies include: Shrek 2, Shrek the 3rd, Pirates of the Caribbean: On Strangers Tides, The Green Hornet, Smurfs and Transformers: Dark of he Moon

EDUCATION

PLATT COLLEGE

San Dlego, CA. Apr. 2008

www.platt.edu

Associate of Applied Science in Graphic Design.

Graduated with honors.